- ssch26802@gmail.com
- 15052251221
- % https://hexiao.vercel.app
- Ind Centre Kwun Tong District Hong Kong

Social networks

- ♥ @tressa eme71692
- **(S)** @live:.cid.b88d16173d943c5d
- @devsirius51

Skills & Abilities

Language

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, Solidity, Rust, C++, Python

Frontend

React/Next.js/Redux Svelte/Sveltekit Vue.js/Nuxt.js/Vuex Angular/three.js PHP/Laravel/Cl

Backend

Node.js/Express.js/nest.js PHP/Laravel Python/Django Go/Rust

Mobile

React Native/Expo Flutter

Blockchain

Solidity Web3.js/Ether.js Rust/Solana Rust/Juno Go/Cosmos SDK

Net Works

Ethereum, BSC, Polygon, Solana, Near

Database

MySQL/PostgreSQL Oracle MongoDB

Languages

English

> CPE: 180/230

Chinese

He Xiao

Full-stack Developer

Passionate Full-stack engineer with over 8+ years experience in software development with Blockchain experience.

Experienced with the latest cutting-edge development tools and procedures.

Able to effectively selfmanage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

Education

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science (Top 10% of the class)

2012 - 2016

National University Of Singapore (NUS) 21 Lower Kent Ridge Rd, Singapore

Work experience

Senior Full-Stack developer(Remote)

01-2018 - 06-2023 Avawatz USA

Project: Development of an Al-supported web application using Bubble + Express.js, connection to the Open Al API and integration of Google's Firebase and MongoDB.

- Mina project: avawatz.com
- Sub Project: Genie, Falcon, Arwen, Zella
- Implemented different wallet connections and contract integrations for multichain support, including
- Ethereum, Binance, Polygon, phantom etc.
- Built a frontend application for minting and staking NFTs using Next and Web3.js.
- Built backend with Node.js and TypeScript to handle transaction reports, billing reports, invoicing systems and
- Developed the frontend with Expo and backend APIs with Supabase for an e-Commerce app.
- Developed hybrid mobile platform for automotive applications using React Native/Expo, resulting in 88%code share between IOS and Android while reducing development time by 33%.
- Deployed and maintained microservices on Google Compute Engine and Google Kubernetes Engine.
- Worked with Firebase to manage database.

Senior Full-Stack Blockchain Developer

07-2022 - 08-2022 Swell Network remote

https://defitankland.netlify.app

https://app.defitankland.com

https://docs.defitankland.com

- Permissionless, non-custodial and liquid ETH staking.
- Staking smart contract using beacon chain (ETH2.0).
- React, Redux, Node, Thegraph, Postgres, Ethers.js.
- CI/CD pipelines and Vercel deployment, Ethdo(Devops)

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERN•

2016 - 07-2017 Vinova Singapore

- Implemented different wallet connections and contract integrations for multichain support, including
- Ethereum, Binance, Polygon, etc.
- Built a frontend application for minting and staking NFTs using Next and Web3.js.
- Built backend with Node.js and TypeScript to handle transaction reports, billing reports, invoicing systems and
- so on for crypto partners for a DeFi project.
- Developed the frontend with Vue.js and backend APIs with Laravel for an e-Commerce app.
- Worked with Firebase to manage database.